Mumma!
Mumma, hurry up now!
Hurry up, Mumma. We're getting late.
Tara, stop nagging me.
-See how it feels?
-Just because she got ready early…
You "nag" me just like this.
Tara!
Again, you've left
the heater in the water!
If there was one thing
you could do properly!
Tara!
What, Mumma?
Please, hurry up.
Come on, Miss Nag-Nag.
Weren't you getting late?
Mumma! Mumma, you are impossible. Mumma!
-Mumma, listen.
-See, I caught you.
Mumma, give me the phone.
-Mumma, phone!
-Here, take it.
Thank you.
Mumma, you know I'm 13, right?
I can go to the school by myself.
-Really?
-Yes.
-I'm serious.
-Oh, I didn't know you were serious.
Good morning, Teacher.
Hello.
Good morning, Mrs. Dsouza.
How are you doing?
How are you?
Good morning, Teacher.
Good morning…
Good morning, Mrs. Dsouza.
How are you doing?
Good morning, Teacher.
Hi. Good morning, Mrs. Dsouza.
So, what are you doing this evening?
-Good morning, Teacher.
-Good morning.
No, no… please ask.
Yes?
It looks a little difficult, Mrs. Dsouza.
-Good morning, Teacher.
-Good morning.
You know, I have dojo after my class.
Oh, no. You don't have to say "please".
All right.
It's okay. I'll be there.
Sure.
Are you sure?
Good morning, Teacher.
Hello, sir.
-Good morning, Teacher.
-Good morning.
Are you sure?
All right, then.
I'll see you.
Good morning.
Look, look! Teacher is here.
Thank you.
So? He comes here every day.
What was that?
I hope you know
that he comes here just for you.
-Are you crazy?
-Yes, I am crazy.
And you're blind.
Teacher comes here just for you.
Yesterday, you were absent.
So, he didn't come either.
Why is that?
How would Teacher know
when I have my day off?
-Even I don't know that.
-Isn't he your neighbor?
He must be keeping a close eye on you.
Like Shah Rukh Khan in Darr.
Please, don't say that.
Good morning.
What if he asks you out on a date?
What?
Good morning, Teacher.
Good morning, Mrs. Dsouza.
You didn't come yesterday.
It's just…
Yesterday… I…
I had… home.
Hello.
I'm Maya Dsouza.
I've just moved into the flat next door.
Would you happen to know any plumber here?
There is leakage in my flat.
Thank you.
Something… at home…
-Egg fried rice?
-Yes, please.
Babu, one egg fried rice special.
It's ready!
-Good morning, Teacher.
-Good morning.
Thank you.
How did you find me?
If you search hard enough,
even God can be found.
You are only my wife.
I have nothing to do with you.
Please, leave from here.
I have just found you after 14 years.
How can I leave without having a chat?
-We have nothing to talk about.
-Of course we do.
In fact, there are
so many things to talk about.
If I started counting them, then
there will be at least
1.5 million things to talk about.
Maya, come here.
Maya?
You changed your name?
And profession.
I can't talk now.
After 2:00 p. m.
-Should I come back after 2:00 p. m. ?
-No.
Not here.
Be there.
Maya.
Good morning, Teacher.
Good morning, sir.
Morning, sir.
-Sir!
-No, Dipok. I don't have time right now.
-Sir, please!
-Dipok, no!
Sir, please!
-Let's go.
-Today, I'll defeat you for sure.
Please win. So I am also free from this.
You really want to lose?
Every teacher
wants to lose to his student.
Let's go.
-Ready?
-Ready, sir.
Okay. One, two, three!
Yes, got it.
I've won.
How? How did you do it?
How many times have I told you,
pay attention to the right thing.
Your duty is to save the coin,
not to defeat me.
Karan!
Hey. Gently, bro.
That was gentle.
-What is it?
-The commissioner wants to see you.
-Right now?
-Yes.
Sorry, man. I have to go.
I have been summoned by the boss.
Lucky boy.
-The boss saved you.
-From?
-My gentleness.
-Karan.
-Go on. That's your chance to escape.
-We're getting late. Come.
Go.
Can I just get a minute, please?
By the watch.
Thirty seconds.
Twenty.
Come.
Time?
Fifty-eight seconds.
Come on. Let's go.
I thought you are going to
get thrashed badly.
Me too.
All the major money-laundering
traders have named Ajit.
He is managing their black money.
Find him.
He's our only link to the racket.
Sir.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
People will just wait for you?
Come here!
One more time!
Again!
Twirl!
Who are you?
-Police.
-Get lost.
We have already paid for the month.
"Get lost"?
You are talking to me as if I'm a beggar.
Hey. Haven't you heard it before?
What?
The sound of breaking bones.
Oh, yes. I have heard it.
Mithun da. Ashanti.  Am I right?
That's great. I am a Mithun fan too.
"Any doubt?"
Too good! Too good.
Just work on that paunch, bro.
What do you want?
You… and our friend here…
So, you are not friends anymore?
Where can I find Ajit?
I don't know.
You, keep practicing.
Don't just stand there.
Think about it.
If Ajit is found,
you will never have to give him anything.
Whatever it is you give him.
Which I know nothing about.
He was here a week ago.
Completely drunk.
He kept blabbering something.
Something about him
winning a lottery in Kalimpong.
"Lottery"?
Soniya.
My darling, Soniya--
Do not.
You're not at all happy
seeing me, are you?
I have changed, Soniya.
I am no longer that man.
-What do you want?
-Listen to me.
I am
quitting the police force.
And the other side businesses too.
Now, I'm going to lead a life of honesty.
Look, you took my money when you left.
I mean, took it or stole it…
I don't know. I have forgotten it.
I have forgotten the past.
You should also forget.
What do you want?
Don't you dare touch me.
I just want you by my side.
Can't we be a family once again? You, me,
and our daughter.
How do you know about Tara?
Tara.
Such a cute name.
One day, she'll definitely be a star.
She looks very pretty too.
She has taken after you.
How do you know what she looks like?
I saw her at her school.
Mumma, where are you taking me?
Mumma, I have tennis practice.
Mumma.
-Good night, Teacher.
-Good night.
TEESTA JUJITSU CLUB
Naren-san.
Practice?
Mumma, I'm bored. What should I do?
Do what you want. Just don't bother me.
Mumma!
Go and finish your bath.
Can I play some music?
Not here. Take it to your room.
Tara, when is your tennis fee due?
Twenty-fifth.
Twenty-fifth…
Who's there?
It's me, Ajit.
Who's here, Mumma?
Just go in your room.
Soniya.
Why are you here? Just leave.
We didn't finish our conversation.
You ran away,
just like you did 14 years ago.
Please, leave.
Or I'll call the police.
Why? I am already here.
I am still a police officer.
Call me.
Ajit…
Please, leave.
Or I will really call the police.
Come on. A husband
is visiting his wife.
Is that a crime?
Go ahead, call the police. I'll wait.
Now, I know where you live.
At least, hear me out.
Please open.
Think about it.
Open it.
What, Soniya…
Shall we sit inside?
No, no need for that.
No problem.
Your home is so clean.
Shall I sit here?
I don't have any money.
Did I ask?
For people like you, money is everything.
And I don't have any.
"For people like you. "
Means?
I am a bad person?
So be it.
Mumma, the heater is not working.
Go back inside! Right now!
I had never imagined
that I will be a father.
And that too… of such a pretty girl.
Wait here.
I'm so sorry.
Everything will be all right, okay?
That's all I have.
This wasn't really necessary.
Please, leave.
I don't have anything else to give you.
Of course you do.
Tara.
Tara?
What do you mean?
You can see a glimpse
of a woman in that little girl.
Have you lost your mind?
It's obvious.
Didn't I say
that Tara will be a star someday?
And when the world sees her,
they will shower money on her.
And on you also,
like before.
-I'm sure, you miss--
-Don't you dare touch me!
Get out of my home.
Soniya.
Maya, Chandramukhi,
Paro, or whoever you are.
You are still my wife.
And… Tara is my daughter.
And this is my house.
I will come whenever I want.
And I will do… whatever I want.
Ajit, please,
don't come back.
I… I will send you money every month.
Please, don't come back.
I can live away from you,
but how can I live away from my daughter?
I have so much to learn about her.
So much to teach her.
In fact, why don't you start teaching her?
Who can be a better teacher
than her own mother?
After that, you can come with us,
or me and my daughter will go.
I am not your daughter!
How dare you hit your father?
Is this what you've taught her?
Ajit…
Come here, my lottery.
I'll teach you how to behave
-just like I taught your mom--
-Mumma!
-Don't touch her!
Soniya!
Don't worry.
I won't leave any marks.
You know it, right?
Mumma! Mumma!
-I'll bury the both of you!
-Mumma!
How dare you hit my daughter?
Mumma!
Let go!
Mumma.
Mumma!
What have I done?
Ajit!
Teacher, it's you.
Sorry, Mrs. Dsouza.
I didn't mean to scare you.
No. It's not your fault.
Are you okay?
Yes. I am absolutely fine.
I… I was just a bit scared.
A cockroach had gotten inside the house.
So… I was just trying to kill it.
-Did you kill it?
-Huh?
Did you kill the cockroach?
Oh, yes. I did.
Thank you, Teacher.
-Good night.
-Good night, Mrs. Dsouza.
Mumma.
We'll have to call the police.
-Why?
-What else can we do?
I killed him.
No, Mumma.
You didn't kill him.
I was the first one to hit him.
Don't you dare say that again.
Do you understand?
No matter what happens.
No matter what they ask you.
You don't know anything about
what happened tonight.
If anything happens to you,
I will die.
What will we do now?
Who is it?
Mrs. Dsouza, this is Naren.
Teacher, from next door.
Teacher, can we speak tomorrow?
I just wanted to ask,
what will you do now?
Sorry, Teacher?
What did you just say?
I just wanted to ask,
what will you do now?
What do you mean?
It's okay if you are calling the police.
Otherwise, perhaps I could help you.
-What?
-Mrs. Dsouza,
it's not easy to hide a dead body.
You may not
be able to manage it by yourself.
Go inside.
Teacher, how did you find out about this?
There is a formula in mathematics.
If A is equal to B is equal to C,
then,
A is equal to C.
I don't understand.
Let me explain.
A is equal to
that stranger
who visited your café this morning.
B is equal to fear.
The fear that appeared
on your face when you saw him.
C is equal to cockroach.
Which created
the same fear as the stranger did.
A is equal to B is equal to C.
The stranger
is equal to fear,
is equal to cockroach.
Therefore,
the stranger is equal to cockroach.
And you yourself said that
you killed the cockroach.
But… how did you know
that he was the same man?
There were some other clues.
Like, a cigarette butt at your door.
The stink of
cigarette smoke in the corridor.
And when I was at the door,
I got a glimpse of
a pair of boots wrapped in a rug.
The size of an average rug
is between five-and-a-half to six feet.
And that stranger
was around 5'11".
You found out everything so easily.
Not everything.
I don't know who he is.
He was my husband.
I got away from him
with a lot of difficulty.
But he found us again.
He forcefully tried to
take away my daughter and…
Before the police arrests me,
should I just confess to them?
Mumma, I will not let you go.
Tara.
Just keep quiet. Go inside.
Mumma,
-but you haven't killed--
-Tara, shut up.
Mrs. Dsouza…
Mrs. Dsouza, the question is,
how will the police view all this.
What do you mean?
It won't be easy
to hide it from the police,
what you are trying to hide from me.
I'm not hiding anything.
Someone tightened a wire
around his neck from behind.
I did that.
And when
he tried to save himself,
someone else held his hands.
His hands have
scratch marks caused by nails.
That was also me.
You would need four hands to do that.
But you have… only two.
If a novice like me
can find out the truth so easily,
then the police
will see through this lie even faster.
Hence, you will have to think
before you call the police.
And what if we don't call the police?
That's a possibility too.
-We're not gonna do anything of that sort.
-Mumma!
Please let Teacher help us at least.
I hope you know
-that he comes here just for you.
-What?
Teacher, if you help us,
won't you get framed as well?
-I am already entangled in it.
-But you haven't done anything.
It's a crime
to hide the truth, Mrs. Dsouza.
Teacher, will you please help us?
If we don't call the police,
how will we hide the body?
-But why should we hide it?
-Then?
Sometimes, telling the truth
is the best strategy.
But before that…
the entire house
needs to be thoroughly cleaned.
Even the cigarette butts outside.
You can do that?
Can you come with me?
Is your husband a policeman?
Yes.
You strangled him with?
The cord of the heater.
Coil heater?
Yes.
You will have to clean it.
No, let it be. I will do it myself.
Was your meeting planned beforehand?
No. He just landed here, all of a sudden.
Then I met him at Lee's.
Lee's?
-The place where couples secretly meet?
-Yes.
Good. The waiters at that place
are used to turning a blind eye.
That… is my money.
Hotel Alice Villa.
He checked in two days ago, and he
made an advance payment for three days.
That means we still have one more day.
Ajit Mhatre.
Assistant sub-inspector.
Mrs. Dsouza…
Mrs. Dsouza, it's very likely that
someone will come here looking for him.
And if he is found…
then… they will find you as well.
What's a simple solution to this?
No body.
No Mrs. Dsouza.
Teacher, I am not understanding this math.
How is this possible?
I don't know.
I'm also thinking.
We need to remove his clothes
before rigor mortis sets in.
What?
You can identify a person from clothes.
The clothes can't be found.
Will you please help me?
Let it be.
You help Tara.
I will take care of this.
Sorry.
Mrs. Dsouza,
we will have to
gather some evidence for you and Tara.
But all the evidence is against me.
We will change
the same evidence to support you.
Thank you, Teacher.
I may not be as good-looking as you,
but I am still alive.
Hey!
What did you do yesterday?
Nothing… I just cleaned the house.
-Nice.
-Thank you.
Hello.
Sub-Inspector Sundar Singh.
Hi. Karan Anand.
But right now,
I'm feeling like Harry Potter.
True, there is magic in our Kalimpong.
-Shall we go, sir?
-But there is no sunlight.
-Nice place.
-Yeah.
Ajit Mhatre.
This was his last known location.
We're trying to trace his cell phone,
but he keeps changing his number, sir.
Kalimpong is not a very big place.
It may take a few days,
-but we'll find him.
-Yes, sir.
-Mr. Sundar will work with you.
-Sir.
I'll give you this photo.
-Send it to all the hotels here.
-Okay.
Teacher?
Good evening, Mrs. Dsouza.
-Teacher, I am scared.
-Why?
You did what I told you, right?
That's all. Then there's
nothing to be scared about.
Good night, Mrs. Dsouza.
Have you seen this man?
-No, sir.
-If you see him, call the police.
Give me something a little more specific.
This area is really vast.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yes, do it.
-Did you find anything?
-No.
Ajit made a call
from somewhere around here.
There is just one network tower here.
But the area
is spread across all sides of the hill.
They will call back from Mumbai.
Maybe we'll get something specific.
-All right.
-Let's wait for a bit.
Okay.
Babu…
-Good morning.
Can I get some hot coffee, please?
-Of course.
-Two.
Can I have one of these?
-Okay.
-And one of these.
-No, no. Only coffee.
-Hey!
One of these too, please.
Okay.
Take a seat. I'll send it.
Okay, thank you.
Ma'am, just one more thing.
Have you see this man?
Here or somewhere around?
-No.
-No?
If you see him,
please call the police station.
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-Good morning, Teacher.
-Good morning, Mrs. Dsouza.
One egg fried rice, please.
Babu, one egg fried rice special.
-Good morning, Teacher.
Morning.
Naroo!
You… Bro, what are the chances?
One out of 95675.
-Wrong. You didn't count me.
-I did.
The current population is 95674.
Naroo! So good to see you.
You haven't changed at all.
Nobody can defeat you
when it comes to numbers.
-How come you are in Kalimpong?
-I'm looking for someone.
Yes.
Okay. Oh, lovely.
All right. Thank you.
Naroo, I have to go now.
But let's meet, okay? Where do you teach?
How did you know that I teach?
Everyone is calling you "Teacher"
as if they are giving attendance
in the class. Tell me.
Mount Hermon.
-Do you know it?
-Yes.
Catch you later. Teacher!
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Teacher!
Mrs. Dsouza, we can't be seen
speaking like this in public.
I know.
-But your friend was asking about Ajit.
-So?
-I think he is in the police.
You did what I told you, right?
-Yes.
-That's it.
If there is anything more
to be done, I will tell you
but we can't talk like this,
in the middle of the street.
-This was the area, right?
-Yeah.
It could be any one of these houses.
We'll have to inquire
in every one of them.
Hello.
Yes. You found it?
Found the hotel.
Alice Villa, on Upper Cart Road.
Let's go.
Are the rooms not cleaned here?
Sir, it wasn't done because he hanged
"do not disturb" sign outside the door.
His luggage is here?
That means he's still here.
-When did you see him the last time?
-The day he checked in.
Sir,
where is Mr. Mhatre?
We are looking for
the answer to that question.
Sir, who will pay my hotel bills?
What's your name?
Sir, it's Pranay. Pranay Chamling.
Mr. Chamling,
do you know anything about this man?
Did he say or ask anything?
No, sir.
But the day he came here,
he was asking about some school.
Wasn't there a school
where we were just now?
-Kamalodaya?
-Yes, sir. That's the one.
-Yes, sir.
Mr. Chamling, he will pay the bill.
Nice room.
What are we doing here?
Waiting.
For?
Ajit has some connection with this school.
Isn't she… the one from the café?
Yes.
Ajit made a call
from somewhere around here.
-Have you seen this man?
-No.
Check until 15 years ago.
Her daughter's age
is around 12 or 13 years.
Mother's name is Maya Dsouza.
-Hello?
-Mrs. Dsouza.
It's me. Teacher.
Teacher,
why are you calling on the landline?
Is there a problem?
No.
But there can be.
-Your friend?
-Yes.
Today, he followed you home.
Mrs. Dsouza, when you got married,
was it registered?
Yes.
Hello, Teacher. Teacher?
Mrs. Dsouza,
listen to me carefully.
Since college days
I know how sharp Karan is.
And I also know
what he is thinking
right now, at this moment.
You are his one and only suspect
in Kalimpong, Mrs. Dsouza.
And very soon, he will come to you.
And he will hound you
until he finds something
or until you confess yourself.
Wouldn't it be better
to tell the police, Teacher--
No.
Just do what I've told you.
Teacher, but I don't know if I can--
You can do it, Mrs. Dsouza.
It's very easy.
When he comes, only answer what he asks.
Else, keep quiet.
Do not say anything on your own.
And yes,
the most important thing.
As far as you're aware,
Ajit is still alive.
But his body?
His body will never be found.
Who found the body?
The monks from
the local monastery found it.
How do you know it's Ajit?
They also found his police ID.
Ram! Santosh!
Move it. Move them from here.
Sir.
Serious, huh?
Where's the ID?
-Hey, ID.
-ID, please.
Give it to him.
Where was it found?
-Where was it found?
-Here.
Blood.
Send this blood for DNA testing.
But what will we compare it with?
Why did you clean the room?
But, sir, you only complained about it.
I…
Oh, man. Mr. Sherling.
Chamling, sir. It's Chamling.
There are no cigarette butts.
Or the glass.
Male. 99% body burnt.
He has been repeatedly struck
on the face with a heavy object.
There is also a deep wound
at the back of the head.
The fingers are 100% burnt.
No trace of the teeth or the eyes.
I believe, whoever has done it,
didn't want him to be identified.
And the DNA test? Did you find anything?
What we found from the toothbrush
and the hair on the comb
matches 100% with the blood.
This is the body of Ajit Mhatre.
-Anything else?
-Yes.
He died on the 10th,
at around 7:00 p. m.
Excuse me.
Yes, tell me.
Found the lottery.
Who is it?
Police. I want to
talk to you about something.
Hello?
Good evening, ma'am.
Karan Anand, Mumbai police.
Tell me.
Ma'am, do you…
Do you know him?
-Yes.
-How?
He is my husband.
But the other day
you said that you don't know him.
Yes.
I don't want him anywhere
around me or my daughter.
I've got nothing to do with him.
What has he done now?
When was the last time you met him?
A few days ago, he visited me.
Ma'am, you will have to
accompany me to the police station.
-Why?
-We
have found a dead body.
Dead?
Ajit? When?
We found it this morning.
That's why, if you can come
for identification.
Please, wait a minute.
Sure.
Behave, you dick.
Did she say anything?
Yes. This time,
she said that she knows him.
-But…
-But?
She is talking about Ajit
as if he is still alive.
How many times
are we supposed to arrest you?
You just don't learn.
How many times more?
Do you… recognize any of these items?
Okay. Take a seat.
Mrs. Dsouza, we know that
Ajit Mhatre was married to
a Soniya Dsouza.
Is that you?
-Yes.
-When did you get married?
About 15-16 years ago.
And your daughter?
From our marriage.
Why was Ajit in Kalimpong?
I don't know.
Why did he meet you?
He wanted money.
He always wanted money.
He never thought about
anything else except money.
Where did you meet Ajit
for the first time?
At Paradise?
Mrs. Dsouza,
we got a photo from Paradise.
This one.
Is that you?
That's you, right?
-Yes.
So, when you were
doing this job at Paradise,
you met Ajit.
What's there to hide?
You could have told us.
-You--
-No.
When I met Ajit,
I was an ordinary girl.
Who fell in love with someone
and she married him.
After that, he sold me to Paradise.
Sold you?
Yes.
Whoever gave you that photo,
you can ask that person.
Sorry.
I will still have to ask you,
where were you on 10th evening?
Am I a suspect?
I am asking
so that you don't become a suspect.
Tara and I went for a film
on 10th evening.
-Where?
-Capitol Cinema.
-When did you leave home?
-Around 5:30 to 6:00 p. m.
And which film was this?
Pets 2.
Tara wanted to watch it.
Did you go back home after that?
No, we went out for dinner.
-Where?
-Gomphu's.
Oh, very good food.
So after that, you came back home.
No. After that,
we went to King's karaoke bar.
For some time.
Karaoke?
Tara wanted to.
Do you do this often?
Seldom. When we have time.
So, you watched a film,
went to a restaurant,
after that, went to a karaoke bar.
Then, you reached home?
Around 11:00 p. m.
May I see that?
Thank you.
What happened?
-Something is not adding up in this story.
-Meaning?
Who goes out on a Thursday?
In the middle of the week?
The girl has school the next day.
Who stays out till 11:00 p. m. ?
But she said that
her daughter wanted to do it.
I think it's nice that the mother
and the daughter get along so well.
Do they get along or are they
cooking up a story about the 10th?
If it's a story,
then, Sundar, my friend,
a very cunning mind is working
behind that beautiful face.
Shall we go?
Naroo?
Naroo!
-Hello!
-Hello.
What are you doing here?
I live here. What are you doing here?
Work.
In the morning, that lady at the café.
Where everyone
was giving attendance to you.
-Tiffin.
-Yes.
Maya Dsouza.
Do you know her?
You must be going to her café often?
I seldom go there. Just sometimes.
She is my neighbor.
But we don't interact much.
Your neighbor?
Have you seen this man anywhere?
Here or somewhere around?
You never forget anything.
No.
Meet Naren Vyas.
The most brilliant student of our college.
A certified genius at math.
That's not true.
Balls, that's not true.
Sundar, this was the final exam of math.
The questions were harder than rocks.
All of us were crying in the exam hall,
like professional mourners.
On the paper, it said
answer any six questions out of ten.
And then he arrived.
He answered all ten questions.
And wrote, "Mark any six out of ten. "
He took the revenge for the entire class.
Wow!
Youth.
You haven't seen him anywhere?
No.
Who is he?
He is the husband of your neighbor.
But… late.
Dead?
Then why are you looking for a dead man?
We are looking for the person
who killed him.
Murder?
You mean, Mrs. Dsouza--
No, standard questions.
-Do you return so late from school?
-No.
Actually, I… was at dojo.
Dojo?
Naroo, you are still at it?
You?
I am coming to your dojo.
We were the best of the best in college.
Naroo could have played
at the nationals if he wanted.
I see. Sorry,
it's hard to believe looking at you.
I'm not.
No. I am visiting your dojo.
We'll have a round together.
-Anytime.
-Okay?
I will get going.
Man,
your neighbor is superhot.
Teacher.
They found the body.
I know.
I met Karan outside.
But you said that they will never find it.
You promised.
Don't worry, Mrs. Dsouza.
I'll take care of it.
What now?
You said what I told you, right?
Yes.
Did they ask anything to your daughter?
No, Tara was inside.
Sooner or later,
they will interrogate her too.
Do you know
what she is supposed to do then?
-Did you show them the film tickets?
-No.
They didn't ask.
Good. Where are they?
I've kept them safely
in the kitchen drawer--
No. Take them out and keep them
in one of the pockets of your clothes.
As if you have forgotten them there.
Nobody keeps film tickets.
-Okay?
-Okay.
-You must be going to her café often?
-I seldom go there. Just sometimes.
Mrs. Dsouza…
Mrs. Dsouza, do the people from
the café know that I go there every day?
What do you mean?
I mean, I'm asking
if the staff working at your café
know that I go there
to get food every day?
Look, look! Teacher is here.
Yes, all of them know.
And everyone likes you too.
Me too.
Do they know that I'm your neighbor?
Yes, it was me who told them.
-Was that a wrong thing to do?
-No.
I'll take care of it.
Teacher…
Thank you, Teacher.
For doing this for us,
thank you.
What happened?
Tara?
Did something happen at school?
Then?
I'm sorry.
Because of me--
You didn't do anything wrong.
You tried to save me, that's all.
Now the police have found the body.
What if they take you away?
Nothing will happen.
No one is going to take me away from you.
Teacher said that
he will take care of everything.
Come on. Go and finish your bath.
It's getting late.
Come on.
I love you.
I am hungry, hurry.
This Maya, Soniya or whoever she is,
why haven't we arrested her already?
-Sir, we just need a little more time--
-Why?
We know that Ajit went
to Kalimpong to meet this woman.
This is the lottery you were
told about at Paradise.
-We have all the evidence, right?
-We do, sir.
But the evidence
is supporting her, not against her.
-On that day, she was elsewhere--
-She is lying! Even you know that.
Ajit is dead. Murdered.
Maya is the only suspect.
What else do you want?
Sir--
"What else do you want?"
I want evidence.
Evidence.
One minute, where had she kept them?
They were in her pants pocket.
Hey, who keeps film tickets?
I would have been suspicious
if they were in some drawer.
-Right.
-But initially she said that…
I must have thrown them away.
Then?
It's possible that she bought the tickets,
but she didn't go to watch the film.
So, you are saying that she bought
the tickets just to create evidence?
If that was her plan, then she would have
given us the tickets the first day.
Perhaps, she was waiting for us to ask.
Her every move is calculated.
Just like in chess.
We will make a move.
And only after that
she will make her move.
She is the mother of a little girl.
You've turned her into
a professional murderer.
Can't the mother of a little girl
be a professional murderer?
Where is the time to commit a murder?
It's not easy
to raise children by oneself.
You seem to know a lot
about single mothers.
My mum was a single mother, sir.
Sorry.
It's okay,
sir.
You see, the time.
It's all about the time, Sundar.
6:10.
So, she went from the cinema to…
7:10.
8:00.
No matter how much kerosene is used,
the human body takes at least…
At least an hour to burn.
-An hour?
-I'm telling you,
returning to the cinema hall
in time after doing all this,
it's… it's impossible.
What happened?
That's it!
That's the mistake she made.
Look, there was just
one reason to erase Ajit's identity.
So that we don't suspect Maya.
Right.
His face was destroyed.
And so were the fingerprints.
Just the clothes were left to be burnt.
She put them on fire.
The clothes began to burn.
She had to leave before
they were burnt completely. Why?
Because she had to
reach back to the cinema hall in time.
What did we find
because of that one mistake?
The blood sample. DNA sample.
We found Ajit. Do you get it?
But if she can prove
that she was at the cinema hall,
then we don't have a case.
The police took the film tickets.
Good.
This was bound to happen, Mrs. Dsouza.
-And yes, Tara--
-Did they ask her anything?
Yes. They had gone to her school.
May I speak to her?
Tara!
Hi.
Do you know this man?
-Did he ever visit your home?
-No.
Good girl.
What else?
He asked me about the film,
if I had watched it or not.
And?
The 10th…
I had my geography exam on the 10th…
Yes! After that,
Mumma and I went to watch Pets 2.
Lovely.
Anything else?
That's all he asked.
Okay.
Good night.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Just one more thing.
Have you spoken to anyone about this film?
To any of your friends?
Yes. My best friend, Maria.
Lovely. Thank you.
Do you have
anything hot to drink at your place?
What is this tradition
of knocking in Kalimpong?
It keeps the joints strong.
Plus, this is a really old building.
Sorry, I don't get many guests.
I can see that.
Coffee?
Yes, coffee, fire, coal.
Give me anything hot.
Please, sit.
Where?
Oh, man!
Naroo,
what the…
Isn't this the one we stole from Regal?
Not we, you.
I just accompanied you.
The person accompanying a thief
is a thief too.
Hey! Be careful.
The poster is very old. It will tear.
Amazing.
What else have you saved?
-Coffee.
-Yes.
Coffee. I feel alive.
Thank you.
What's this?
They are math problems.
And how many years
I will take to solve them.
Seriously?
Are you still madly in love
with mathematics?
Who else will love me?
That is also true.
But one must make an effort because…
-"Efforts lead to success. "
Are you saying
this will take 15 years to solve?
Yes. I mean, if I can give it all my time.
Once, it took me ten years
to solve a problem.
And then?
Somebody solved it two days before me.
What?
So, ten years of hard work
went down the drain.
What did you do then?
I would have been devastated.
By the way, you have
maintained yourself very well.
We are the same age,
but you look half my age.
-You also have a full head of hair.
-That's true.
You will lose in just four moves.
Who do you play with?
Myself.
You have such a hot neighbor
and yet you play with yourself.
Sorry. Bad joke.
But really hot.
I mean, the coffee is really hot.
And I need your help
regarding the hot neighbor.
Why?
Your hot neighbor
is currently my hot suspect.
Mr. Late?
Correct.
Mrs. Dsouza… is a suspect for that?
Not just a suspect, my friend,
she is the one and only suspect.
-No.
-Yes.
Will you keep an eye on her?
Look, I wouldn't have asked,
if you were not her neighbor.
Just keep a lookout
for anything suspicious.
How can Mrs. Dsouza be a murderer?
She is a simple, family-oriented lady.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
Mrs. Dsouza,
you forgot to sign here.
-Thank you.
Mrs. Dsouza…
What now?
I thought it was you.
I just saw you
in front of the police station.
Just now?
You have quite a sharp vision.
I meant… a little while ago.
Didn't you… pass by the police station?
Are you following me?
No. Why did you feel that?
Because even when my daughter lies,
she behaves just like this.
-I wanted to talk about your husband.
-Can we do it some other time?
-I'm getting late--
-It's a bit urgent.
I have to go to work.
We have to speak.
Do you have a warrant?
Mrs. Dsouza, do you watch a lot of TV?
No, I don't have a warrant.
But I'll get one if you insist.
But if I come to your café with a warrant,
it won't look good.
Especially for your business.
Don't be so angry.
I won't take much of your time.
-Naren sir.
-Yes?
The principal wants to see you.
Mrs. Dsouza, if you don't mind,
can I order something to eat?
I don't know what is it about this place,
but ever since I got here,
I am always hungry.
You already are eating into my time.
Might as well eat some food.
-Brother.
-Yes, sir?
What's good here?
Sir, Dragon bar, so dragon momos.
Dragon momos. Are they good?
Yes, the momos here are famous.
Done. Get me the famous momos.
A plate of pork momos. And get
the special ghost pepper chili sauce.
But, ma'am, won't it be too spicy for him?
Don't worry about it.
Just do your job.
Wow, you can speak Nepali.
-We ordered the famous momos, right?
-Yes.
But they would be a bit spicy.
Don't worry, I was born to eat
spicy food, ma'am.
I'm getting late.
Everything that you did on the 10th,
can you narrate it one more time?
Again?
Again.
Please.
Naren, for the term exam, please set
the math paper a bit less difficult.
But less difficult, I mean, why, sir?
Parents are complaining.
The kids don't understand
the level of your math homework.
The parents don't understand.
Even I don't understand it, sir.
Sir, but the questions are not difficult.
They just appear difficult.
They only need a bit of logic.
Naren, the kids come here
to get a high school education.
Not a PhD.
Thank you.
Would you…
Ajit…
Why did your husband come to meet you?
I already told you. For money.
The man who
hadn't met his wife for 13 years,
who had never seen his daughter,
he came to meet you just for money?
Why is that so?
You'll have to ask that to Ajit.
Mrs. Dsouza.
-I hope it's not too spicy.
-Not at all.
Why would anyone
come to Kalimpong to kill Ajit?
You want me to do your job also?
You have to go.
I met you just to say
that the murderer of your husband,
he is roaming free.
Or she is roaming free.
So please be careful.
If you see or find anything abnormal,
then please inform the police.
That's it?
That's what you wanted to tell me?
Yes.
You were worried
as if I was about to arrest you.
Next time, just call me
to the police station.
Oops.
Brother, do you have sugar?
What is sugar called in Nepali?
Please, give me.
-Dipok.
-Yes, sir?
Do you find my math papers hard?
Super-hard, sir.
They go right above my head.
Then raise yourself.
The world will not come down for you.
I'm missing you
Missing me?
Not me.
Naidu.
He is calling us.
-He has some new information.
-So do I.
So stupid.
Tara watched Pets 2
without watching Pets 1.
What is she going to understand?
But she didn't want to
understand the plot.
Just wanted to show us
that she was elsewhere on the 10th.
Correct?
You okay?
I don't know, man.
I had something at Dragon Momos.
It's threatening to come out.
-You had the ghost pepper chili sauce?
-What's that?
It's the special sauce
of Dragon Momos. Very spicy.
But they don't give you that
unless you ask for it.
Shall we go?
Well played, Mrs. Dsouza. Bravo.
Look at this.
This man was strangled before being burnt.
Really?
These marks found on the neck
are caused by a thick wire
wrapped in felt cloth or by a cord.
Like the cord of a heater?
Exactly.
Just like the cord of a heater.
In fact, I think the wound
on the back of his head
is caused by the rod of the heater.
Water heater?
Coil water heater. There's one
in every bathroom of Kalimpong.
Doctor, where is the bathroom here?
Maya,
look, look, that handsome man.
-Hurry up and close the shop.
-Why?
-Prema, don't argue. Close it.
-Let him come inside.
Give these two the bill
and get rid of them. Come on.
Let it be.
Oh, God. He saw me.
Sir, one game? Best of five! Sir!
This time, I will definitely win.
-Or else, the coin is mine.
-Done.
-Okay, thank you.
-Thank you.
Prema, hurry up and close it.
Come on, come on.
Sorry, are you closing?
-Yes.
-No.
Thank you.
One, two, three!
-Again, sir.
-What's the point?
-This time, I'll win--
-Dipok, you are not paying attention.
The score is three-zero.
Even if you win, the coin is mine.
Do you understand or
is this also going above your head?
Do you need anything?
-Do you serve momos here?
-Yes.
-The momos of Tiffin are the best.
-Really?
I love momos.
In fact, today I had them at Dragon Momos.
Oh, Dragon Momos!
I hope you didn't have
the special chili sauce.
Special chili sauce? What's that?
You didn't have it, right? You were saved.
It's the hottest sauce of Kalimpong…
It's the hottest sauce in the world.
-Rubbish.
-What do you mean by "rubbish"?
Don't you remember
that two people had to be hospitalized?
-What?
-Yes.
It's a good thing
that we didn't order that.
It's not given to anyone
other than the local people.
Prema, come on, finish the cleaning.
Did you hear that?
People had to be hospitalized.
-I could have died.
-It's nothing like it.
Maximum one can get
is a stomachache because of it.
But still… sorry.
Mrs. Dsouza,
a sorry won't cut it
for the way you have made me suffer.
You'll have to make up for it.
Naroo! Hey, Naroo!
You looked lost.
Were you solving a math problem?
No.
-Student problem.
What happened?
I have a student.
I… scolded him too harshly today.
Is he a good student or a bad student?
There are no bad students.
-"Only bad teachers. "
But you must be setting
a super-hard paper, right?
No.
It's not that hard.
I want them to use their brains,
not just memorized formulas.
If I hide an algebra problem in a geometry
question, they should be able to catch it.
An algebra problem in a geometry question?
Man, you are such a cruel teacher.
If I don't do it,
then these kids will never think.
They'll just believe what is told to them.
They'll never try to find the truth.
Are you aware of
the "P is equal to NP" problem?
No. It goes way over my head.
P is equal to NP states that,
for any given problem,
either we find the solution ourselves,
or we accept the solution
given to us by somebody else.
For example?
There are five birds sitting in a tree.
If I shot one,
how many birds will be left on the tree?
-Four?
-Yes.
-Correct?
-Correct.
What is it?
See, I gave you a solution
and you accepted it.
Yes.
But had you thought a little,
then you would have understood
that after hearing the gunshot,
there won't be any birds left on the tree.
All of them would fly away.
The truth was right in front of you,
but you didn't see it.
Is this math or logic?
Math is logic.
Anyway, what are you doing here?
Are you here to see me?
You know the hot suspect, right?
I need to ask her some questions.
But…
Hello.
Mrs. Dsouza, you know Naren, right?
Naroo, Mrs. Dsouza is forcing me
to go to some karaoke bar.
Will you join us?
I have work. I need to check some papers.
Both of you go ahead.
Shall we go?
Thank you for bringing me here.
I have never been to a karaoke bar before.
But there are so many
karaoke bars in Mumbai--
Hello and namaste, everyone!
My sweet Kalimpong people,
how are you doing tonight?
-Great!
Okay!
And you already know what day is today,
and what's going to happen?
-Yes!
Okay.
What's going to happen?
Today's Tuesday, right?
Yes, today is Tuesday.
What happens on Tuesdays?
They have a karaoke competition
here on Tuesdays.
Let's leave before it begins.
Just five minutes.
Let's go after listening to
one song. Please.
Here we go.
Time to sing and time for a song.
Just make sure, you don't get it…
-Wrong!
Here it comes. Song number one.
Come on, someone!
Anyone?
Which song is it?
Come on. It's such an easy song.
-…song that everyone knows.
-You know it?
How can I forget it?
She knows it.
Oh, wow! That's more like it.
-Ma'am knows it.
-Have you lost it?
-Please, give an applause for ma'am.
-Don't be shy, just sing.
I want to go home.
First, the song and then home.
-Come on. Please.
-No, not now.
-Please.
-Everybody, she is here.
A round of applause for ma'am.
Come to me
My love
My heart is longing for you
It waits for you with hope
Don't make me beg my love
-That's it? One more time, please.
-No.
One more time, please.
Just one more time.
Come to me
My love
My heart is longing for you
It waits for you with hope
Don't make me beg my love
Come to me
My love
My heart is longing for you
It waits for you with hope
Don't make me beg my love
We have a winner here.
Thank you.
Because of you,
I got to enjoy momos and karaoke today.
Thank you too.
I don't even remember
the last time I had so much fun.
Didn't you just go there last week?
That was for Tara.
I have to go.
Good night.
Was she here on the 10th?
My heart is longing for you…
No, I don't think so.
Yes, Sundar. Did you get it?
Mumma…
Tara?
Didn't you sleep?
Mumma, the police came home.
When? Who?
Some Sundar Singh.
He took the coil heater.
-The same which--
-Yes.
It's probably Teacher.
He had called a while ago
to ask if you've returned.
-Hello?
-Mrs. Dsouza…
Teacher, police were here--
I know. I heard about it.
But, Mrs. Dsouza,
why did you go with Karan?
He wouldn't get off my back.
So I thought, let me go with him
and put an end to it.
What… What happened there?
Nothing.
He repeatedly kept asking
the same question,
"What happened on the 10th?"
That's all? That was it?
Yes.
It was their plan.
One of them will take you out
and the other one will take the heater.
Why?
Because they have found out
what was used to kill Ajit.
The police still suspect you.
And they will inspect everything.
Mrs. Dsouza, you will
have to be a bit careful.
Yes.
So,
did anything else happen?
-Where?
-With Karan…
I mean… at the karaoke bar.
No.
Good night, Mrs. Dsouza.
Mumma, didn't you go with Prema Auntie?
No.
Why will I go with Prema?
Did you ask Teacher before going?
I am not his student,
that I have to ask him.
And
what if he stops helping us?
Thank you.
No.
This coil heater doesn't match.
This isn't the murder weapon.
So, are we closing the case?
Just in Kalimpong.
We will continue it in Mumbai.
So all the evidence
provided by Maya Dsouza was true?
All of them.
I got a call from the karaoke bar
confirming that
she was there on that night.
Then who killed Ajit?
I don't know, sir.
Until now, the suspect was Maya Dsouza.
Now,
it's "X".
Suspect X?
Yes, sir.
Suspect X.
Mrs. Dsouza, can I have two minutes?
-I'm busy.
-Just two minutes.
By the watch.
What is it now?
Do you want to go to Gomphu's
to find out if I went there also?
Just like the karaoke bar?
What to do?
Police work is like this only
and we have to do it.
But after today, I won't bother you.
I just wanted to tell you that.
I am going back to Mumbai.
I have to go. I have customers.
Sure.
Keep visiting us.
Please, keep visiting us.
Take her out.
She's always working.
She doesn't think about herself.
What are you saying?
I am sure she has a lot of admirers.
There is nobody, except Teacher.
Teacher?
That one. Your friend.
-There is nobody except--
-Just a minute, Naroo?
-But he hardly comes here.
-What are you saying?
He comes every day, like the sun.
Prema!
By the way, you have
maintained yourself very well.
We are the same age,
but you look half my age.
You also have a full head of hair.
Naroo, Naroo, Naroo.
On the 10th,
Naren, Naren…
On the 10th…
Mr. Naren had taken a leave on the 10th.
Oh, my God,
in so many years,
this is the first time he took a leave.
Hello.
-Hello.
-Come on.
I am fine here.
Hey, don't be scared. Come in.
Do you remember? "Fall seven times…"
"Rise on the eighth. "
…three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine…
Sorry, I… didn't know you were waiting.
I thought we could go back together.
I wanted to talk to you about something.
What did you want to talk about?
This case…
and that hot suspect.
I wanted to thank you.
Thank you, for what?
Do you remember?
You told me that sometimes we cannot
see the truth that's right in front of us.
Yes, so?
I was making the same mistake.
Regarding this case.
I kept looking at Mrs. Dsouza
and kept wondering,
"How do I catch her lies?"
And what was the truth
in front of you that you couldn't see?
Her truth.
I didn't think once
that everything she said
could be true.
So that means
Mrs. Dsouza didn't commit the murder?
Look, the evidence stating that
she was elsewhere on the 10th is solid.
But if there was someone else
who was helping her?
That is possible.
Where were you on the 10th?
Now I am a suspect?
Well, I am the police,
I have to ask these questions.
I was at home the entire day on the 10th.
I wasn't keeping well.
If needed, will you be able to prove it?
No.
I didn't know any of this,
else I'd have saved some evidence.
Hey, don't feel bad,
but I'll have to arrest your Mrs. Dsouza.
My Mrs. Dsouza?
Stop pretending.
Prema was saying that
you go to Tiffin just for her.
Yes, I do. Sometimes.
She said, "Every day,
like the sun. "
Listen, Naroo…
I would have gone too,
if I had a hot neighbor like her.
Not once, I would have gone
many times a day.
There is one thing
which is still bothering me.
Will you help me a bit?
What is it?
Whoever the killer was,
he made sure that
Ajit could not be identified.
So that nobody suspects Mrs. Dsouza.
But he didn't burn the clothes fully.
He left them half-burnt.
It would have taken just five
more minutes to burn the clothes.
Why would the killer do that?
You are the police.
I'm just a math teacher.
Teacher.
What happened?
I'm not able to understand.
Initially, the police said
that they don't suspect me.
Then… they started asking about you.
About me?
What did they ask?
-Please, don't get angry--
-Why would I be angry…
Please tell me.
The police were asking
and my staff told them that you
come to Tiffin
just for me.
As if you are in--
No. Why… What… I mean…
Why would I do that?
Yes,
I also told them many times
that there is nothing between us.
But…
I don't know why they said that.
That
you are in love with me.
They should be
paying attention to their work,
but they kept talking about us.
I told them so many times
not to pay attention to such things.
It won't cause a problem, right?
Sorry, you
are angry, right?
Not at all.
In fact, I'm happy
that you told me.
Anyway,
they have made their move.
Now, it's our turn.
Our turn?
-Yes.
-Mumma…
Good evening, Teacher.
I will be back in a moment.
Mrs. Dsouza,
you will have to make a promise.
No matter what happens,
you and Tara will stay out of all this.
As if nothing happened.
Don't do anything.
Don't say anything.
That's the only way you both can be saved.
I don't understand.
I will…
I will explain it to you later.
Don't use makeup.
You look prettier without it.
Good morning, sir.
Sir!
One round.
-But you don't have the coin.
-You do.
-Ready?
-Ready, sir.
One, two, three!
Finally! I won!
You're a zero divided by an egg!
A zero divided by an egg?
This formula went right above my head.
Okay. Bye, sir.
She couldn't have done it alone.
Someone has helped her.
She is a sly one--
No, man! We are troubling
Mrs. Dsouza for no reason.
It's proven that she's got
nothing to do with the murder, right?
I'm telling you,
she is the murderer,
and someone else
has helped her get rid of the body.
Who?
Do we have any evidence?
Do we have anything?
We don't have anything.
You are unnecessarily
slandering Mrs. Dsouza.
-What?
-Sir, come quickly.
Now what happened?
Say it again.
I killed Ajit Mhatre.
And I did it as per Maya Dsouza's request.
You should arrest her as well.
Babu, the fried rice?
Mrs. Dsouza, you will have to
accompany me to the police station.
-I'm a bit busy right now.
-It's urgent.
-I am working.
-Me too.
Do you have a warrant?
Yes.
I saw him on the 10th for the first time.
-He was roaming outside our building.
-Who was he?
Ajit.
However, I didn't know who he was then.
I don't know anything.
Why would he kill Ajit?
Then?
Then I went and asked him.
He said that he's Maya Dsouza's husband.
And that Maya wanted to meet him.
Right then, I realized that he was lying.
One minute…
How did you know that he was lying?
Because Maya used to tell me everything.
She also had told me that she
never wanted to see her husband again.
I never told him anything of that sort.
But you had told me that
you don't know Mrs. Dsouza that well
and you don't interact much with her.
That's what we tell everyone.
Excuse me?
I am Maya Dsouza's bodyguard.
And it's my duty to protect her.
We don't want people talking about us,
so we keep our relationship a secret.
I am a teacher at a school.
People can say all sorts of things.
He came to the café every day.
We also made fun of him.
But he was like any other customer for us.
You… never told me anything.
What kind of an idiot are you?
Why would I tell you? Who are you?
Nobody knows. Not even her daughter.
Then what happened?
Ajit wanted to meet Maya.
I took advantage of it.
I told him she's visiting
someone near the monastery.
And he believed you?
What does he know about Kalimpong?
He didn't even know
which road lead to which place.
He was delighted just to get the address.
He was quite a stupid man.
Just a minute…
You made a plan to kill Ajit
the moment you met him--
Absolutely.
If anyone tries to harm Maya,
it's my duty to eliminate that person.
-How did you kill him?
-By strangling him.
I didn't have time to buy things,
so I took a coil heater from home.
I also took kerosene and a matchbox,
so that he is not identified
and Maya doesn't become a suspect.
Of course.
And then?
Then I saw him.
He was looking for Maya
at a desolate place.
Didn't I say that he was a stupid man?
Then I followed him.
And with the metal end of the heater
I hit him on the back of his head.
Then I wrapped the cord around his neck
and tightened it from behind.
I practice jujitsu every day.
I have a lot of strength.
But anyway,
it wasn't as difficult
as I thought it would be.
-What did you do after killing him?
-First, I took off all his clothes.
Then, using a big rock,
I cracked open his face.
Just like how a coconut is cracked open.
So that his face is not identifiable.
Then I burnt his fingers
using the lighter.
So that he is not identified
by his fingerprints either.
Then I poured kerosene on him
and burnt him completely.
Matches.
Only the murderer can tell so accurately
how the murder was carried out.
And then?
Then I set his clothes on fire.
But the flames were going too high,
I thought someone might see it.
So I left from there.
Did you tell Mrs. Dsouza
that you have killed Ajit?
No.
I didn't want to risk it.
Women can't keep a secret.
So, when did
Mrs. Dsouza ask you to kill Ajit?
-She would secretly tell me everything.
-How?
She would speak in her apartment,
and I would hear it
through the hole in the wall.
Sir, sir.
Hey! Be careful.
The poster is very old. It will tear.
You would listen to their conversations
without their knowledge?
No.
She would herself tell me secretly.
She would act
as if she was talking to her daughter,
but in reality,
she would pour her heart out to me.
I didn't even know about it.
Tara is my best friend.
I tell her everything.
So, that was your way to find out
everything about Mrs. Dsouza?
What do you mean, "find out"?
She'd tell me herself.
But she never spoke to you directly,
right? Maybe, you misunderstood--
Nonsense!
She told me!
Who speaks to their daughter like that,
that her husband harasses her
and she wishes that he dies?
You are in the police,
please use your brains.
She was talking to me.
She was asking for my help secretly!
It's possible.
Sometimes you end up saying such things.
The hole in the wall…
does she know about it?
No. It wasn't needed either.
Every day, I would inform her
that I have reached home.
And if she has any problem,
she can tell me about it.
How did you inform her?
I'd give her a missed call.
If after five rings,
she answered and disconnected the call,
that meant everything was okay.
And if she didn't answer,
that meant
she wanted to tell me something.
On the pretext of talking to her daughter.
Does Mrs. Dsouza know about these calls?
Yes. You can ask her.
What? No.
Three months ago,
someone began calling me.
I'd get a call every evening.
Around 8:00 to 8:30 p. m.
He began telling me about myself.
As if someone is secretly watching me.
I got scared.
So I stopped answering the calls.
But why did you decide to tell us
everything all of a sudden?
Because she betrayed me.
Had I known she would betray me,
I would have never killed her husband.
She turned me into a murderer.
-She should be punished as well.
-What do you mean by she betrayed you?
Oh, man!
Do you mean, me?
Naroo, we don't have
anything like that between us.
Don't you lie, Karan.
I saw you both at the karaoke bar.
I'm not blind.
I know what I saw.
I knew that Teacher likes me.
But I didn't know
that he would go to such lengths.
Someone used to write
strange letters to me.
I would throw away most of them.
But I kept these three as evidence.
"Don't use makeup.
You look prettier without it. "
"Let me know if you need any help.
You looked worried today. "
"Karan, I'll never forgive you…"
Sir, this was found too.
Karan!
Yes.
This is the murder weapon.
Doesn't it sound strange?
Yes, sir.
This man is also a bit strange.
Since college.
They say,
"There is just a thin line
between genius and madness. "
Are you sure that he murdered Ajit?
One hundred percent, sir.
He knows all those details
which only the murderer would know.
And the coil heater found at his apartment
contains Ajit's skin samples.
That is the murder weapon.
And Maya?
All of her alibis are strong, sir.
All the claims about
the places and times made by her
-have been verified by the witnesses.
-All right.
Create a murder charge sheet on Naren.
Let Maya go.
Yes, sir.
Mrs. Dsouza, you can leave.
You're free to go.
May I speak to Teacher once?
Why?
I wanted to ask him why he did all this.
Mrs. Dsouza, he is not
in the right state of mind.
-I'll come with you.
-No.
He won't say anything in front of you.
For my peace of mind,
please let me speak to him alone.
Please.
Good evening, Mrs. Dsouza.
Why are you doing this?
This is wrong.
For the one who saved my life,
I can certainly do this for her.
Me?
When did I?
Do you remember the first time
you came to my house?
To ask for the plumber's number.
That day, I was about to hang myself.
Why?
For my first love,
mathematics.
There was a problem that I was
trying to solve for the past ten years.
And when I finally solved it,
I found out that
46 hours ago, someone else solved it.
I felt my life ended there.
And that's when you knocked on my door.
-I don't know how can I thank you--
-I should be thanking you, Mrs. Dsouza.
For taking me back
to my first love.
-I'll come to visit you every day--
-No.
Please.
There is another math problem
for which I will need
at least 15 years to solve.
Let me spend this entire time
with my mathematics.
Only then I can do it.
Please… look after yourself and Tara.
Thank you, Teacher.
Thank you, Mrs. Dsouza.
Hey!
This woman is a murderer!
Don't let her go! Don't let her go!
She is a murderer!
Catch her!
-Why are you letting her go?
-Let's go, ma'am. He has lost it.
Why are you letting this woman go?
She is a murderer!
Didn't I say,
nobody can take me away from you?
Teacher took care of everything.
How?
I don't know.
I could never understand math.
Are you aware of
the "P is equal to NP" problem?
P is equal to NP states that,
for any given problem,
either we find the solution ourselves,
or accept the solution
given to us by somebody else.
Mrs. Dsouza,
we will have to
gather some evidence for you and Tara.
But all the evidence is against me.
We will change
the same evidence to support you.
One dead body of Ajit.
One and only suspect, Maya Dsouza.
Because Ajit died on 9th,
and Mrs. Dsouza has no alibis for the 9th.
But…
If Ajit died on the 10th,
she can have all the alibis.
Therefore,
till 9th, the suspect is Maya Dsouza.
But on 10th,
the suspect becomes X.
You need to die one more time.
And that stranger was around 5'11".
Hey.
Hotel Alice Villa.
He checked in two days ago, and he
made an advance payment for three days.
That means we still have one more day.
Teacher, I'm scared.
Before the police arrests me,
-should I just confess to them?
-No.
Just do what I've told you.
When he comes, only answer what he asks.
Do not say anything on your own.
And most importantly,
as far as you're aware,
Ajit is still alive.
But his body?
His body will never be found.
You strangled him with?
The cord of the heater.
We need to remove his clothes
before rigor mortis sets in.
You can identify a person from clothes.
Teacher,
will you please help us?
Don't worry, Mrs. Dsouza.
I'll take care of it.
There is one thing
which is still bothering me.
Whoever the killer was,
he made sure that
Ajit could not be identified.
But he didn't burn the clothes fully.
He left them half-burnt.
Why would the killer do that?
Nothing will happen.
No one is going to take me away from you.
Teacher said that
he will take care of everything.
I killed Ajit Mhatre.
I am Maya Dsouza's bodyguard.
It's my duty to protect her.
See, I gave you a solution
and you accepted it.
But had you thought a little,
then you would have understood
that the truth was right in front of you,
but you didn't see it.
Is this mathematics or logic?
Math is logic.